[{"answer": " Well there's something new", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Talk away, Professor", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You know that's what it is.  Mrs. my friend tells me you're here at all hours", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I care more about my life.  And yours", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what... come by for dinner in a week and I'll show you", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I can't do that", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "\"Elo", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, I guess you'd call us... New Yorkers", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well it seems like a long time", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The journey is part of my work", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ah... no", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "'Fraid so.  Just a regular old... mud carrier", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I might find the truth rather hard to understand?... Can you go back", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'll take you tomorrow... You must have seen a lot on your journey", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Every night", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "We share everything", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What's it all for", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I mean, why do you do it?  What purpose does it serve", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I must say, you look remarkably good.  You don't want a book then", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm the librarian.  I've always been the librarian", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Morlocks", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Who doesn't know the Morlocks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You know of them", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Do you know where they live", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Why should I help you?  You primates", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "THEY TOOK MY ENTIRE RACE", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "The air... the power", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The Morlocks didn't build this", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "This has to end", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "This has to end", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You came underground when the world was ending above.  And you evolved. Some into the Morlocks and others", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Created", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "And what of the my friend", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No... they didn't survive only to be your food.  You did that", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No... they didn't survive only to be your food.  You did that", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "But this is barbaric!  Have you completely lost all sense of", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why would you let me go back", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm glad he's gone.  Maybe he's finally found a place where he can be happy", "docId": "TheTimeMachine.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "His home", "qsentId": 40}]